# **ADENIYI BELLA**

#### CIVIL ENGINEER/SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/SOLUTION ARCHITECT

+49 1789703022

✓ adeniyibella@gmail.com

Berlin, Germany (Open to Relocation).

in linkedin

**3** Gi

<u>Github</u>

<u>Portfolio</u>

### PROFILE

A Civil Engineer with many years of experience in the construction industry. I took up software development to support the technological advancement in solving some of the challenges faced in the construction industry. These challenges include stagnant productivity, cost overrun, rework due to poor project execution. The knowledge gained (academically, professionally and self development) is very much applicable in other professional industries.

### **EDUCATION**

#### CAREER FOUNDRY SCHOOL, BERLIN

07.2022 -

Fullstack Dev.

01.2023

 Project based, practice oriented, remote, collaborative coding training

#### TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY MUNICH

04.2020 -11.2022

M.Sc. Civil Engineering

• Thesis Topic: LPG or RDF as graph data for modelling construction data

### RECENT EXPERIENCE

#### **WOLFF & MUELLER GMBH, STUTTGART**

12.2021 -Present

#### JavaScript Developer/Process Automation

- Introduced code quality checks with linters into our workflow. This improved the readability of codes, and ensured a standard is followed across board.
- Switched the code base from jQuery to react framework and synchronous to async JS. This ensured that we could switch to the new version of the SaaS product the team relied on.
- Automated several manual processes which helped to improve the workflow, user's experience, and worker's performances.

#### TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY MUNICH

10.2020 -10.2021

#### **Research Assistant**

- Worked with a group of Ph.D. researchers on the topic of 3D scanning of buildings and applying Al in construction.
- Created building models in blender software, labelled them into different classes, and fed the classes to a ML model for semantic segmentation and classification of the classes.
- Created a script in python that helped to optimize the number of scanning points required for a 3D laser scanner.

### **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

- JavaScript/HTML/CSS
- React/Angular/Redux
- Node JS/Express framework
- TypeScript
- SQL/MongoDB/GraphQL
- Python
- Rest API
- Al Quality assurance

## PERSONAL SKILLS

- Fast Learning
- Problem Solving
- Adaptability
- Stress Tolerance
- Leadership
- Team Work

### **LANGUAGES**

- ENGLISH Native
- GERMAN A2/B1